So we're going to try to do the Lion Dance.
The morning is a good time
at Expo Nation, okay, but you need an
explanation.
Sol
Grindr lines times during the
Lion Dance and Stephen's medium-tension bag,
more dancing through different
levels of meditation. Minor in defense
of nine or ten different levels of
meditation,
and that's why it's called dance.
In everyday life,
this area is that part of this idea is to
familiarize yourself with meditation.
Touristically, meditation, you know what
the three types of meditation are.
Santiago, I, as Ser Gomez,
I started doing a meditation where
you do a review of what
you learned. It came
to Vanessa Benitez. It's a measurement of
planning, problem-solving.
Wise Mayans came to me because
my husband yells at me in yoga, and I, with Yo Gomis, and
one of the light, the most to that fact, with you
choose an object to focus on,
like the eyes of the soul of New Holder, and
what you hold in your mind, you
concentrate on that meditative object. I have, let's say, in a specific way, in
slang, Deeper and Charger, the Dandy, see in
front train, and then  As you
concentrate more, you begin to enter and
delve deeper into that
meditative object. The dream of the down, I enter into
hunger, okay?
So when you enter and delve deeper into
an object, and the art of
Ken Read and Time, let's define it, okay? That way
of entering and concentrating on a
meditative object has 10 levels. You enter,
passing, going up in 10 levels. There are
two locks that I'm going to do with those
ten levels with you.
Wow, wow, protest!
Let's practice that on the main stage
in the dance and the water and the air.
/ Igor to change the violin of Bach from the
leader of that show, American star
in the lion dance. You go up, you go down, you go up
and down, and other rooms you come out, and
then there is a meditation that is above
all that. You have
3.
We are going to do it after the dance, the
Lyon, there is the dance, the Lyon, and then the
meditation that you are above, and the
tradition is to do the dance, the
Lyon, first and then do the meditation where you are
above all that. It has 90 levels, the
extension
and the lion dance. So you are
penetrating the object, levels it has
Rivers ten camera on YouTube
camera which is what it's called drill like
a drill drills inwards in one
direction and to come out further in the
opposite direction outwards they have in
tap meditations work with
Caracol Radio audit and the meditation which is
above or on top of a violin
words
camps drills perforated within the
nine levels
and then there is a zero because actually there
are ten levels of Nigran Taiwan and
then you go back to one already lose then you
jump to zero
TV2 Yampier jumps 6033 champ tetrica
606 I the entity so when drilling
within the meditative object
but to do to improve your
mental flexibility light world before you
know compact min
Jordan corten and no line and jumper am if
you start to drill 7 you go down to 0 drilled
eight you go down to zero and so it goes up and
down and you see your
mental flexibility within the meditative object the
necessities and you have to do this
exercise it helps you
directly perceive emptiness locate this Sean
has 19 to Stevie Award and nine
because to perceive the  emptiness
directly you have to move in those
the voice is actually 10 levels
new slave is the lowest level is the
mind of the realm of desire
this mat of mind your heart is the
state of mind you have as a state
of almost all day
Darwin Jin Qing to cappuccinos when you
are having a cappuccino of my disease
define America that's
when the mind is definitely
not in meditation of mining and some
of time
inside
the mind is concentrated on an
external object and is not withdrawn inwards so that it is
called Playacar to be
our Stanford is in the objects of
the senses outwards has desire
ground state of mind and the mental state of the
realm of desire
eras
this country has two parts two
components two characteristics
sculpture painting although it touches
extends I say that being here in
Santiago Bitar and Habitat which is now
called Topáter Pan is in yoga is
another decade of definition avoid
headboard in Honduras in Camps in this
Pan highlighted
the define that definition comes in the
text that Stanley Bando is translating
where are you so and Pando
and not even definition all to attack
Attacking that,
the main one which we sizwe, colorful Chinese art,
is the definition, it's the mind that is
generally conscious of its
object,
wells, the derby, interest in aesthetics,
and then there's the mind that pierces or
penetrates, delves deeper into the
concentration of the object, and now
come the details, zinc, zinsa
sheen, refers to the
general characteristic, the main thing of the object, to the
need to change, it intimidates me, I
like to compare this to listening to
music, I dream in America in 2000, therefore,
to pain, General Mills Inc.,
when you're in a supermarket in the USA and
they're playing horrible music
and I don't like it because I know their
intention is to play music for people
my age, to clap, night insists, admits
they're playing terrible music, well, terrible
pop music from 1968,
neon spikes and board, I'm waiting for the ghost
stories, detective, because they know that the
only people who have time to
go to the supermarket during the day are
60-year-old people, which I don't
like,
so I try not to listen to it
and sometimes I try to understand the song
like Jimi  Hendrix with very impugna very
bad
telefe com in sambeat
western music arts store but if I go
home and someone asks me there was
music in the supermarket picasa heart
beat arca raf awareness a 15 you must
mythic test now because I have bitar
cate a general awareness and I can
say if there was music online richard
ambiente driving home pitcher means
that driving on the way home android
music of my ipad and I'm playing music
line a default from my phone in has been
singing outside of the air of live and it doesn't
have outside suddenly put on
a song I like the night
drive
organic so that I put a
real stereo in my car we took out the original and
put in a new one
what is the definition of a real
stereo you
see sadly the one who plays the bass, that
is, the basses that sound very good
very good
the main thing of a monastery is the bass
of nothing
amnesty you must meninas and when I'm getting to
know my house I listen to the bass
tomtom
and period
[Music]
go out into the snow this country there is nothing
and all you can add is the bass
to scale  Go down and light page nine and
ask other people
how you like the bass in this song.
In this case, there's a bass in this song
suitable for Europe. They have a top
and you can inhabit the box, sign them up, they
have bitar here, and I have
business bichar of interest. They're just
listening to the song, the violent one from
Page Park, and I'm drilling and
deepening the bass. The bass music
heard in the low sun of the time, 'state
of mind' for meditations for fish and
for the effects of meditation. The
lowest state of mind and your mind closes is
the mind of the kingdom, the desire in the
healthy baby GMT. The dollar
there comments
since it has a very primitive level
in English. No admin, your report doesn't think
that Lloyd Webber also negotiates.
It's a very low level of noticing
something. For example, if you're in the
supermarket, you're
not... I noticed there was
music. Yes, I noticed, but it's like
very general. The healthy one, you weren't
specifically listening to the music
of anything, but it's like an awareness of the
object, but without a show, with very little examination
and analysis,
especially for the objects of the
kingdom of...  desired like food or
music of this air Maineri GMT the
mental state of consciousness is a
very primitive or very basic state
and in Buddhism what there are other realms
that they call the realm of form and the
realm of formlessness show index I feel
very nice pressure in this world if you
are a very good person in the realm
of desire year and make gray karma and
sow very good karma
you can't be point in the former you can be
reborn in the realm of form split
after dying at 16 like a western
put on the east
before such this point of the dance
Punta del Este
as Punta del Este former that would be the
realm of form couples picking all
the men so handsome
the reason why they call it the realm
of form and avoid Sony Life and the
Star
because it is that everything there is a
five-star hotels the fountains
fountains campsites many fountains in Paris
see people
all very beautiful Webpulse having come out
pipe in start and serve furtive
beautiful people among them to give firm of going to
India disarm if you meditate a lot in the
realm of desire makes of that  and the Caribbean
burning in such a way that you have the there is a great
possibility that it will be reborn in the kingdom the
form of three hits see and fame to this
artistic development
many masters indicate that this is a
place you shouldn't go there to
garden picas
fund tv / state council on my trip
because in those places they are having
such a good time that they are not
interested in coming to a retreat the
hunger
here there is line master of people universe
reinhard like most people in
Guadalajara and the United States at this
moment since Deneuve and Martin are even
more unnecessary and if you continue and
measure more in the kingdom of desire
greater forms you can be born in the kingdom
of no form a form is alive
donaba grosso physical for in that kingdom
people do not have a dense physical body
to leave only they have plane or energy a
physical energetic body that is physical
and they still have
iuc patxi for the concept that the
mind as a rider is mounted on a
horse which is the energetic plane and
has of Sharon if you die in the kingdom of
desire year and Merinas Carmack fat
forms round which is reader pont is
reader widgets housing facing east and
if you generate  You have enough good karma and
women in the realm of desire, but
you have karma part of the realm, the form,
like the richest house in Punta del Este,
the place where there is no bard, there is no why,
because there you don't have to go anywhere
from the moment you are a spirit
between one birth and another rebirth
of PPC for State Farm, which is art,
Puente del Este,
the purpose of the bard is to arrive from
Guadalajara, Fil de Guadalajara, Punta del Este, it
goes of forms and football, inter-
formation, but if you were born in the realm
of the norm, it is not Paraguay, there is no
bard there
and there nobody
starts to live here where you died,
if you generate the karma to be reborn in the
realm of formlessness, of IFAI, if I
die now sitting here inside,
inside the realm of formlessness, to
whom it is not because it has no place, no
location, there is no place,
well, and we
chatted, and the realm of form and the
realm of formlessness, each one has
four levels, there are
four levels in the realm of form
and four levels in the realm of
formlessness,
two of three, and many times the masters
speak of the nine levels of the  three
kingdoms one design lab at one level of the
kingdom the desire to form the voice 44
levels of the kingdom the form in force
form online bull and four levels of the
kingdom the non-form in nine in total
for being born in the four above of
form and non-form at 8 and James Jones
Jr.
To do this you have to do
special meditations in the kingdom of
desire already Fort
the testing bag and therefore
entered that type of meditations
are deeper meditations that
pierce more into their meditative object in
the kingdom of desire and I injected it were
pierced more they penetrate more into the
object they see 4 level of index life
index air during this life within the
kingdom of desire will provide the
youth to live in a form and if you do that a
lot it will cause you to be born into the kingdom of
form and of the ancient Oliver
if you learn to go deeper to penetrate more
into the meditative object outside of
brakes which are four levels that you
go into added Aralar index
line and you practice it a lot in this life
job and therefore forms Velarde was  the voice
reborn as in one of the four
levels of the kingdom of the form nothing in
testing ovary
wilde -five that I have in front of this
film 'the long island because there is the
American ok
because this prop is like the
Latin American Riviera because you think it touches you
that causes you and the tip of the east if you
meditate a lot
Girona if you meditate a lot you don't have the
opportunity to misbehave you can't
lie and that at home you can't
design Steve Austin Jackson Scandar
Touring Meditations it's difficult to have
inappropriate sexual conduct during
meditation
show in English and 6 by default and by
default
you are reborn in a good place
that you didn't have the opportunity to sow
bad seeds ok as long as
they have something interesting about this
and the channel if you understand replay and
necessary round state of mind' snap to
know if your mind is in a
mental state of the realm of desire it is impossible to
directly perceive emptiness efe in
the snub round state of mind' Rafita
Cara will sign if you are in a
mental state of the realm of desire that he
signed have cappuccino if you are
tasting a cappuccino from the abdomen at
that moment and has a cyan passport has
this graphic it is impossible to
directly perceive emptiness and one more to
form a mastermind you have to be in a
meditative state of the realm of
unnecessary form within a body of the
realm the desire of tarija setar so
the body of the realm the desire has to
sit at an hour
your hands character put your hands
properly engine modular and almost
close your eyes on the main
interactive material and the mind has to
pierce penetrate its concentration
within the meditative object of mind they
make you cause of form the mind does not enter
within the realm of form of mind
cost of meditation witwer
foosball of form help already at the moment
the mind enters and penetrates the
meditative object which causes you to be reborn in a
realm of form if at that moment you
die
the mind we say the main extender form
barac min
the mind making arma and let me in a
unitary way at the moment we say that the
mind is in the realm of form but
in reality
entering a deep meditative state
which generates the karma which would
cause you to be reborn in a realm of
form if  at that moment you would die show
one shant inlac of that that 10,000 are still
black seen I mean it's something city and
music in the supermarket design
that's the mind the kingdom of desire would
attack me and vol
in the United States they did something very bad
about Starbucks and it didn't achieve its history
they put Starbucks boxes in all the
supermarkets the times of Zarautz,
Estermann, York and black people and this is not even
Tibet Line Team Six Day of Music with
Starbucks coffee
this is this the mind the kingdom of is you
are in a supermarket listening to the
music of 1968 with a Starbucks coffee
Starbucks is drinking a
Starbucks coffee initiate me or if you are a man
Joaquim find out if all progressive you
are asking everyone
where the toilet paper is from the
toilet paper that this shipment of friends
because the man never goes to the
supermarket to leave the pay per capita ends
so you are in the mental state of the
kingdom of desire until the toilet paper
cappuccino bad music of the accident
about employment that employs Stockton River
of my Hendrix and by  And accidentally
one of the good employees of the
store
puts on Jimi Hendrix in the
underground music Ralph Awareness Internet and
the raw consciousness, the
general consciousness of the senses, rivers
of Perth and Adelaide, pierces and
penetrates a little his concentration within
him of how he's playing the bass in that
song, he starts to hear the bass, there
are chairs within a
mental state of the realm of desire to see, but you
already enter a higher level, granting
Starbucks, you already forgot to be, you already
forgot the toilet paper and 'management'
indicates in Jimi Hendrix's Space Line and
there you are, your
shopping cart and listening to it, the bar,
especially the bass within the song of
Jimi Hendrix's Undefeated System Jennings,
and because Jimi Hendrix
classifies, in turn the
shopping cart disappears, even the
baseline, with it, even the
bass appears, your consciousness of concentration on
the bass in the air is very classic and you
go like that
and everyone wants you to have a
heart attack while you're standing in a
round way, Esther  Mine, that's the state of
mind of the kingdom, the form, well, it's Frank
the music, the enjoyment, the ecstasy of
music. In English, with our watch, in
English we say, I forgot where I was.
Nobody is good, internet without broadcasting,
just go in and go in, into the enjoyment, I went into the
enjoyment of music. That's the first form
of style showed the merit of
ACS in the most superficial meditation.
Okay, from this bikini, auto meditations
for form forms, that's just the
beginning of the measures of
meditations, 4 the kingdom of form and 4 the
kingdom of non-form. In index,
form a new one and in air lines and in the
first, the first state of mind, the kingdom
of form for my design award, so that
of all the seed, part of your mind
says I don't want to go back to thinking about
toilet paper
and is also waiting, I hope they
put on the song, the long version of
this song by Jimi Hendrix, Backstage
Minister's Crimes, so I can stay
here for eight minutes instead of three to
fifteen, to imagine locking Mario Main
and software articles, history, part of
your mind is aware of the
supermarket spar and mind now  Monaco is
part of this whole gene in Jimmy Hendrix
Iron and denied me Page Line and Wanna Be
in the Player has Hendrix part of your
mind says I don't want to go back to listening to
the bass between the Jimi Hendrix song I
just want to stay here in the enjoyment of
this
and this blog, I
mean the bad supermarket pop music
is the lowest of the kingdom,
desire tends to baseline code and then to
delve deeper and starts listening
to the song Still Desire is still the
kingdom, the desire of the honey type and
then they put on real Jimi Hendrix very
good First for Me and that's when you enter
the first of the first level of the
kingdom, the formality, Crucis topless and so the
supermarket enjoyment of being given and
being a river of tissue,
this is where you truly begin to meditate
on it, they know modeled and
from here there are seven more levels that
love form, three more within the kingdom of
form
and four within the kingdom of norm,
Steinman, you have 99 options, regret the
kingdom of desire, four form four of the
kingdom of form, four the kingdom
of no form, which one is most info
which of these levels is
the most useful platform for procedures and the
team is to directly perceive the
emptiness of the web
park where benefits are already starting
more wants to park here on the first
level of the kingdom the way do
n't go further don't go deeper
with fire right that it is
deeper than that me what difference
between and I know what the difference is
between these eight there is California in a
gane teacher I went and investigated
and I'm going to show you right now
and each of those levels we are going to
try to practice it today the
first time point in which is the first
important thing to say is hunger
citywire happens indio I am going to
show you what happens in each of
those states of Bergara chartered
we will try to practice the choice to
football degenerates into hockey into
saving snacks in Nerja but it's not going to
happen to you because it's not possible that that
happens in that sitting in a hotel here
a chat for various life art life
imagination meditations but it is similar
to meditation where we imagine
our past life and good medicine
in re  Quality, you're not going to be seeing your
past life, Bayern and starting
movie passes, but you do, but by doing that,
the process of perceiving your past life begins. It wo
n't be a direct perception of your
past life, and the bar that includes it is paid for,
but it will give you clues. Nobody, child, peace,
life will give you clues of your past life by
doing the exercise of imagining that
you had a past life. You can see the seeds of the past
life, credit imagination from YouTube,
because the seeds of the past life
generated the seeds of the imagination
that you generate. It's in visualization.
5 says the same for these 8. Maybe you
can, manager of the first. Perhaps you will be able
to enter the first level,
Haidar, manager of the nexus,
indestructible. I doubt you will manage to enter the
next seven today
in this room, and Tex, Pau, in water,
Abdi meditations, and Nieves know that it
takes you about an hour of
deep meditation to enter any of those
seven levels. That's why I
tell you to meditate for an hour a
day. You have to defend me, Neves. That
hour a day includes the preliminaries. No,
you're not well, clarity, and dedication. And it
includes dedication, no, not so much Qing
Wang. Let's see.  I'm talking about an hour
of deep concentration, no music,
where you don't hear the music or
even the bass. Juan Abal, like that, I do
n't have it. I'll wait for you
now. Yes, I'm going to take him to the hospital.
The Way Extension Fund show, today we're
going to have fun. Try Mindstorms. This
music was going to do the Lyon dance
like a kitten,
and by definition, he says, "I went and gave them the
definition of these 8, enable, right,
name, and it's going to hit us. Everyone talks about
them, but nobody knows what they are. From
Huentitán, layer on top of people
on fire, so I went with his dad and
other people and got them the
CLYFC of Bering, of the Virgin of
Guadalupe, like a possession. The judges,
Guadalajara, to the beach, still, when I
was researching and preparing this
text, I was in the truck. We
were in the truck and there was a
procession of the Virgin of Guadalupe.
There are horses, two with hats. The
racing is located, destatis, I'm like a bird, they
title it. Let's see if being better, where the
traffic was very slow because there was
a procession of the Virgin of Guadalupe
with horses and everything."  Coming from the
airport here, only pickup of lasting
author d argent and because we received
the blessing of the Virgin of Guadalupe,
so because of the blessing of the Virgin
of Guadalupe, I had enough time to
research and teach you this, which I
teach today,
and then you have to thank
the two most important people who
provided you with this room: Capa and
the Virgin of Guadalupe,
and they are working together.
Although sometimes I was in the
diamond business for 19 years, we
were also the
smallest diamond jewelry company in the world and we
became the largest in the world.
We had Esther Merino Arts in Cell
Syntax 2 of Team Movistar. They have in
Texas in 100, they have 15,000
jewelry stores and public campsites,
but the levels compete with those
companies that said we can be
and they call it living and living. Living is
marching, which is the competition that
they define with the initials "live," and that
are three companies that have better quality
from the SAS free and no standard sit with
chip and not a mere mere
gave me class, that is, it has  Jewelry that
is intended for a middle-class market
of nothing
stations and they compete a lot for
advertising space on
Texas television channels
and you see the two women talking in one
love my heart bin hammam in my boyfriend
smith investment look my boyfriend asked me to marry him
and for me this hand and
look at the diamond he bought me
organic widget in which it has I'll
buy it for you and Carl French
maybe the lip doesn't want you
and the other company then puts an
ad
look a boyfriend asked me to marry
him
where he bought the ring I lived in my
envy embi
or husbands catch it's stupid to pay so much
of the ual the artist in such necessity I
lived and one day he sends an order to
Vivienne I saw a
higher quality jewelry and a
lower quality one at the same time in the same
package of diamonds
and from that package of diamonds from that
batch of diamonds we would take 10% of the
best quality 2 goals from Vivendi
these were going to see they lived well and the
other was going to do
and then he would send them two packages of
diamonds both companies
and then it was  I was filling out the
application form and putting the
address on the insurance policy,
and then I thought there's a mistake here,
the address is the same for both water companies. So I went up to talk to my boss, and he said, "Thanks, lazy bum," and I said, "Hey, there's one of these addresses further back, and it's because the address
is the same for both companies."
Mysterious, nobody came, and it's 15
women, made, Times Company, it's the same
company, men, type, they're the
same owners of the Teic Cristales sector,
and they'll have TV, but on TV they
criticize each other, and they added
Whitman Water because they don't
care which store you go to, Bellis Magnetic
Uruguay, they just want you to go to one
of the two. Uayma trackback, what I'm talking about
is because I'm talking about this, Virgin, Virgin, they're
layered with layer, that seems to be the case in Camping,
and the Virgin of Guadalupe and Jets are layered,
it belongs to the same company,
don't tell an old lady.
[Music]
It's true